kvcwebsitehosting.com 2017-06-30

# KVCHOSTING Privacy Policy

KVCHosting.net, LLC is committed to protecting client data collected. KVCHosting respects client's privacy and use of KVCHosting services indicates agreement to KVCHosting privacy policy guidelines as defined:

KVCHosting will collect and record minimum required client information in order to provide competitive services. KVCHosting privacy policy states the kinds of processes that may occur in different circumstances when client data will be collected. Usage of KVCHosting.net grants the right to collect user information. 

KVCHosting may record any or all information given by client according to transaction type client enters, such as date of birth, name, address, phone numbers, fax numbers, email addresses, website use, and other personal information needed to process request. 

KVCHosting will strictly use required information and data on client to process request or task made. KVCHosting will enforce reasonable measures needed to prevent unauthorized access to such information. In certain cases, KVCHosting may require additional forms of identity from client to safeguard such information. 

Client internet browsers have in-built mechanisms to store small files or cookies that have information to help websites recognise client account. KVCHosting may use such facility to increase user experience. However, user may choose to prevent user computer from accepting cookies, which may impair some of the website's functions. 

KVCHosting will not disclose any personal information received from client to third parties. KVCHosting may use such information to notify or inform client about developments and other KVCHosting services or offers. However, client or user will be given the option to remove self from such a mailing list or notification processes. KVCHosting will not disclose information collected on website to third parties without consent and acknowledgement from client/user. KVCHosting may provide general survey or data information to third parties but will withhold those that may identify individuals. 

**U.S.-EU & U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks**  
KVC Hosting complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. KVC Hosting has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view KVC Hosting's certification, please visit [//www.export.gov/safeharbor/](https://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

**DISCLOSURE TO LAW ENFORCEMENT**  
KVCHosting reserves the right to disclose subscriber information to law enforcement agencies without consent or notifying subscriber if lawful request is made from such agencies. KVCHosting will cooperate fully with such law enforcement agencies. 

**POLICY CHANGES**  
KVCHosting may change its Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Reasonable steps will be made to inform clients/users. However, clients are encouraged to check for updates every time they enter the website to ensure it meets their approval. Changes will be made directly to Privacy policy and such future changes will supersede the prior version. 

**CONTACT US**   
Clients and users are encouraged to contact KVCHosting directly if any questions should arise or they need clarification about information collected. Factual errors in such information or removal of details from list under KVCHosting may also be made this way.
